const contest_1_1 = [
    {
        "S/N": 1,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Distinguish between reptiles and amphibians with respect to the following.",
        "Question": "Type of respiratory organs",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "The respiratory organs in Amphibians are gills, skin, and lungs, whereas reptiles have only lungs",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 2,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Distinguish between reptiles and amphibians with respect to the following.",
        "Question": "Reproduction Type",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Amphibians are oviparous organisms, whereas reptiles can be oviparous or viviparous",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 3,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Distinguish between reptiles and amphibians with respect to the following.",
        "Question": "Mode of fertilization",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Amphibians exhibit external mode of fertilization, whereas reptiles exhibit internal mode of fertilization",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 4,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Describe chordates with respect to the following.",
        "Question": "Body temperature",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "They are either cold or warm-blooded organisms",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 5,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Describe chordates with respect to the following.",
        "Question": "Type of blood vascular system",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Have a closed vascular system",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 6,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Describe chordates with respect to the following.",
        "Question": "Germ layers",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Triploblastic",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 7,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Find the values of the constants $a$ and $b$ if the straight lines",
        "Question": "ax $+5 y=3$, and $4 x+$ by $=1$ intersect at the point $(2,-1)$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$a=4, b=7$\n$[2 a-5=3,2 a=8, a=4,8-b=1, b=7]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 8,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Find the values of the constants $a$ and $b$ if the straight lines",
        "Question": "$3 x+a y=4$, and $b x-5 y=6$ intersect at the point $(2,-2)$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$a=1, b=-2$ $[6-2 a=4,2 a=2, a=1,2 b+10=6,2 b=-4, b=--2]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 9,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Find the values of the constants $a$ and $b$ if the straight lines",
        "Question": "$a x+2 y=-3$, and $2 x+$ by $=6$ meet at the point $(1,2)$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$a=-7, b=2$\n$[a+4=-3, a=-7,2+2 b=6,2 b=4, b=2]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 10,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Solve for $\\mathrm{x}$ if the determinant of the matrix $A$ has the given value.",
        "Question": "$\\mathrm{~A}=\\left(\\begin{array}{cc}2 x & x \\\\ 3 & x\\end{array}\\right), \\quad \\operatorname{det} A=5 \\quad$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$x=5 / 2,-1$\n$\\left[2 x^{2}-3 x-5=0,2 x^{2}-5 x+2 x-5=(x+1)(2 x-5)=0, x=5 / 2,-1\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 11,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Solve for $\\mathrm{x}$ if the determinant of the matrix $A$ has the given value.",
        "Question": "$\\mathrm{~A}=\\left(\\begin{array}{cc}3 x & 1 \\\\ x & 2 x\\end{array}\\right), \\operatorname{det} \\mathrm{A}=7 \\quad$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$\\mathbf{x}=7 / 6,-1$\n$\\left[6 x^{2}-x-7=0,6 x^{2}-7 x+6 x-7=(x+1)(6 x-7)=0, x=7 / 6,-1\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 12,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Solve for $\\mathrm{x}$ if the determinant of the matrix $A$ has the given value.",
        "Question": "$\\mathrm{~A}=\\left(\\begin{array}{cc}3 x & 2 \\\\ x & 5 x\\end{array}\\right), \\operatorname{det} A=1 \\quad$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$\\mathrm{x}=\\mathbf{1 / 3},\\mathbf{- 1 / 5}$\n$\\left[15 \\mathrm{x}^{2}-2 \\mathrm{x}-1=(3 \\mathrm{x}-1)(5 \\mathrm{x}+1)=0, \\mathrm{x}=1 / 3, \\mathrm{x}=-1 / 5\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 13,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "A uniform meter stick of negligible mass is balanced on a knife edge with two masses placed at various positions on the meter stick.",
        "Question": "Find the mark at the position of the knife edge when the meter stick is balanced with a $40 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $15 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark and a $60 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $60 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$42 \\mathrm{~cm}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 14,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "A uniform meter stick of negligible mass is balanced on a knife edge with two masses placed at various positions on the meter stick.",
        "Question": "Find the mark at the position of the knife edge when the meter stick is balanced with a $20 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $20 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark and a $30 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $70 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$50 \\mathrm{~cm}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 15,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "A uniform meter stick of negligible mass is balanced on a knife edge with two masses placed at various positions on the meter stick.",
        "Question": "Find the mark at the position of the knife edge when the meter stick is balanced with a $15 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $20 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark and a $35 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $60 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$48 \\mathrm{~cm}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 16,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The radius of curvature of a concave spherical mirror is $0.32 \\mathrm{~m}$. Find the magnitude of the lateral magnification produced by the mirror of an axial object placed $0.80 \\mathrm{~m}$ from its vertex.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "0.25",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 17,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The radius of curvature of a concave spherical mirror is $0.25 \\mathrm{~m}$. Find the magnitude of the lateral magnification produced by the mirror of an axial object placed $0.75 \\mathrm{~m}$ from its vertex.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "0.20",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 18,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The radius of curvature of a concave spherical mirror is $0.20 \\mathrm{~m}$. Find the magnitude of the lateral magnification produced by the mirror of an axial object placed $0.15 \\mathrm{~m}$ from its vertex.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "2.0",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 19,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Consider the following elements, listed not in any particular order.\nBeryllium, Argon, Silicon, and Sodium.",
        "Question": "Which of these elements has the lowest first ionisation energy?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Sodium",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 20,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Consider the following elements, listed not in any particular order.\nBeryllium, Argon, Silicon, and Sodium.",
        "Question": "Which of these elements has the biggest atomic radius?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Argon",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 21,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Consider the following elements, listed not in any particular order.\nBeryllium, Argon, Silicon, and Sodium.",
        "Question": "Which of these elements is most electronegative?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Silicon",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 22,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "In the commercial preparation of trioxonitrate(V) acid, nitrogen(IV) oxide dissolves in water to give the acid while nitrogen(II) oxide is evolved. The balanced equation for the reaction is as follows:\n$3 \\mathrm{NO}_{2}+\\mathrm{H}_{2} \\mathrm{O} \\rightarrow 2 \\mathrm{HNO}_{3}+\\mathrm{NO}$.\n$\\mathrm{O}=16.0 ; \\mathrm{N}=14.0 ; \\mathrm{H}=1.00 . \\quad$ The molar volume of a gas at STP is $22.4 \\mathrm{dm}^{3}$.",
        "Question": "Calculate the mass of $\\mathrm{HNO}_{3}$ that can be produced from $69.0 \\mathrm{~g}$ of $\\mathrm{NO}_{2}$ gas.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$3 \\mathrm{NO}_{2}+\\mathrm{H}_{2} \\mathrm{O} \\rightarrow 2 \\mathrm{HNO}_{3}+\\mathrm{NO}$.\n$3 \\times 46.0$\n$138 \\mathrm{~g}$ of $\\mathrm{NO}_{2} \\quad \\equiv \\quad 126 \\mathrm{~g}$ of $\\mathrm{HNO}_{3}$\nTherefore, mass of $\\mathrm{HNO}_{3}$ to be produced from $69.0 \\mathrm{~g}$ of NO${ }_{2}=$ $(69.0 / 138)^{*} 126 \\mathrm{~g}=63.0 \\mathrm{~g}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 23,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "In the commercial preparation of trioxonitrate(V) acid, nitrogen(IV) oxide dissolves in water to give the acid while nitrogen(II) oxide is evolved. The balanced equation for the reaction is as follows:\n$3 \\mathrm{NO}_{2}+\\mathrm{H}_{2} \\mathrm{O} \\rightarrow 2 \\mathrm{HNO}_{3}+\\mathrm{NO}$.\n$\\mathrm{O}=16.0 ; \\mathrm{N}=14.0 ; \\mathrm{H}=1.00 . \\quad$ The molar volume of a gas at STP is $22.4 \\mathrm{dm}^{3}$.",
        "Question": "Find the volume of $\\mathrm{NO}_{2}$ at STP that can be used to produce $189 \\mathrm{~g}$ of $\\mathrm{HNO}_{3}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$3 \\mathrm{NO}_{2}+\\mathrm{H}_{2} \\mathrm{O} \\rightarrow 2 \\mathrm{HNO}_{3}+\\mathrm{NO}$.\nMoles of $\\mathrm{HNO}_{3}$ in $189 \\mathrm{~g}$ of it. $\\quad=189 / 63.0=3.00$\nMoles of $\\mathrm{NO}_{2}$ needed $\\quad=(3.00 / 2.00) * 3=4.50$.\nHence volume of $\\mathrm{NO}_{2}$ at STP required $=4.50 * 22.4=100.8 \\mathrm{dm}^{3}=$\n$101 \\mathrm{dm}^{3}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 24,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "In the commercial preparation of trioxonitrate(V) acid, nitrogen(IV) oxide dissolves in water to give the acid while nitrogen(II) oxide is evolved. The balanced equation for the reaction is as follows:\n$3 \\mathrm{NO}_{2}+\\mathrm{H}_{2} \\mathrm{O} \\rightarrow 2 \\mathrm{HNO}_{3}+\\mathrm{NO}$.\n$\\mathrm{O}=16.0 ; \\mathrm{N}=14.0 ; \\mathrm{H}=1.00 . \\quad$ The molar volume of a gas at STP is $22.4 \\mathrm{dm}^{3}$.",
        "Question": "Calculate the mass of the minimum amount of water required to react completely with $44.8 \\mathrm{dm}^{3}$ of $\\mathrm{NO}_{2}$ at STP.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$3 \\mathrm{NO}_{2}+\\mathrm{H}_{2} \\mathrm{O} \\rightarrow 2 \\mathrm{HNO}_{3}+\\mathrm{NO}$.\nMoles of $\\mathrm{NO}_{2}$ in $44.8 \\mathrm{dm}^{3}$ of the gas at STP $=44.8 / 22.4=2.00$\nMoles of water required $=(1 / 3) * 2=2 / 3$\nMass of water $\\quad=(2 / 3) * 18.0=12.0 \\mathrm{~g}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    }
]

export default contest_1_1